http://www.aquamaster.ca/privacy-policy

HomeAquaMaster Advantages
Doing More. Using Less.How to CompareTop 10 ReasonsCertificationsAbout UsTestimonialsVideo ArchiveAbout Water
Hard WaterCommon Water ProblemsCommon Water Treatment TechnologiesHow Softeners WorkFAQsBenefits
Soft Water BenefitsDrink to Your HealthWater Saving TipsProducts
Water SoftenersBenefitsProductsFeaturesSpecificationsWarrantyCertificationsWater Softener that Does MoreDrinking Water SystemsBenefitsProductsSpecificationsContact Us
Customer ResourcesWarranty RegistrationWarranty Part RequestFind a Local DealerBecome A DealerContact UsBlogDealer Login
HomePrivacy Policy
Privacy Statement
Revised and posted as of: October 12, 2005
AquaMaster.ca is committed to safeguarding your privacy online. Please read the following statement to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of the AquaMaster.ca Web site. The AquaMaster.ca Web site is owned and operated by AquaMaster.ca
If you have any questions regarding our privacy statement, please feel free to contact us by e-mail at info@aquamaster.ca.
Gathering of Information
Voluntary Submission
AquaMaster.ca does not collect personally identifying information about any individual AquaMaster.ca Web site user except when knowingly provided by such individual. For example, we may ask you for information when you register for a contest or survey or to receive a newsletter. You always have the option not to provide the information we request. If you choose not to provide the information we request, you can still visit most of the AquaMaster.ca Web site, but you may be unable to access certain options and services.
Cookies
A cookie is a data file that certain Web sites write to your computer's hard drive when you visit such sites. A cookie file can contain information, such as a user identification code, that the site uses to track the pages you have visited. AquaMaster.ca uses cookies solely to track user traffic patterns throughout the AquaMaster.ca Web site. We use this data on an anonymous basis and we do not correlate this information with personal data of any user.
Most Web site browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser settings to display a warning before accepting a cookie, or to refuse all cookies. However, if you choose to disable the receipt of cookies from our Web site, you may not be able to use certain features of the site.
Browser Level Information
AquaMaster.ca Web servers automatically collect information about a site user's IP address, browser type and referrer by reading this information from the user's browser (information provided by every user's browser). This information is collected in a database and used--in an aggregated, anonymous manner--in our internal analysis of traffic patterns within our Web site. This information is automatically logged by most Web sites.
Use of Information
Our primary goal in collecting user information is to enhance your experience on our Web site. We achieve this goal by, among other things, providing interactive communications such as our electronic newsletters to the e-mail address that you provide to us, and developing future editorial content based on your interests. To develop content targeted to your interests, we use aggregated user information to determine which areas of our Web site users prefer based upon traffic to those areas. We do not track what individual users read, but instead how well each page or content area performs overall.
AquaMaster.ca may also disclose information about our users when we believe, in good faith, that the disclosure is required by law.
When you are on an area of AquaMaster.ca and are asked for personal information, you are sharing that information with AquaMaster.ca as well as business partners and vendors providing hosting and other services for AquaMaster.ca If you do not want your information to be shared, you can choose not to allow the transfer of your information by not using that particular service. These parties, as well as advertisers who contract directly with a third-party service to serve their advertisements, may set their own cookies.
In addition, any personally identifiable information provided by our users as part of an advertiser promotion online may be provided directly to advertisers.
Please be aware that AquaMaster.ca sponsors, advertisers or Web sites that have links on our site may collect personally identifiable information about you. The information practices of those parties and Web sites linked to AquaMaster.ca are not covered by this privacy statement. AquaMaster.ca users should also be aware that, when you voluntarily disclose personal information in chat areas or bulletin boards, that information may be collected by others and may result in unsolicited messages from others.
Kids under 13: Do not send any information about yourself to us--including information such as your name, address, or e-mail address. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. In the event that we learn we have collected any personal information from a child under the age of 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information from our database as quickly as possible.
E-Mail
AquaMaster.ca respects the privacy of its readers and shall not disclose, distribute or rent its e-mail subscriber newsletter list to any third party, nor shall it permit anyone else to do so.
How to Contact Us
If you have any questions regarding our privacy statement, please feel free to contact us by e-mail at info@aquamaster.ca.
This statement may change from time to time, so please check back periodically.
© 2007 AquaMaster.ca All Rights Reserved.
DEFINITIONS:
IP address: Every computer connected to the Internet has a numeric address called an “IP address." This may or may not correspond uniquely to a particular computer. In some cases, IP addresses can be resolved to domain names, which may indicate a site visitor's Internet service provider, employer, university, etc. As part of its database analysis AquaMaster.ca resolves IP addresses to domain names.
Browser type: A user’s browser is a software program running on a computer that allows users to access documents on the World Wide Web. Browsers can be either text or graphic. They read HTML coded pages that reside on a server and interpret the coding into what the user sees as Web pages. Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer are examples of Web browsers. Browser type typically discloses hardware platform, operating system, and browser software and version.
Referrer: The referrer is the URL of the Internet resource or page that causes a browser to request a page or image from AquaMaster.ca servers.
AquaMaster Advantages
Doing More. Using Less.
How to Compare
Top 10 Reasons
Certifications
About Us
Testimonials
Become A Dealer
About Water
Hard Water
HomeAquaMaster Advantages
Doing More. Using Less.How to CompareTop 10 ReasonsCertificationsAbout UsTestimonialsVideo ArchiveAbout Water
Hard WaterCommon Water ProblemsCommon Water Treatment TechnologiesHow Softeners WorkFAQsBenefits
Soft Water BenefitsDrink to Your HealthWater Saving TipsProducts
Water SoftenersBenefitsProductsFeaturesSpecificationsWarrantyCertificationsWater Softener that Does MoreDrinking Water SystemsBenefitsProductsSpecificationsContact Us
Customer ResourcesWarranty RegistrationWarranty Part RequestFind a Local DealerBecome A DealerContact UsBlogDealer Login
